Guide to the New York State Board of Mediation Cases 1952-1964
New York State Board of Mediation Cases
- AR 3751 - AR 4050 (1951). (Box 52)
  - Reliable Optical Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Sonotone Corporation, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - 2160 Anthony Avenue, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - 1325 and 1337 Boscobel Avenue, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Henri's Restaurant, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - AAA Television, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - University Loudspeakers, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Pipe Protection Service, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - 105 Lorimer Street, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - 213-223 Bennett Avenue, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - 3451-55 Knox Place, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - T White UPH Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Ace Slip Cover Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Kings Electronics Corporation, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Milbee Furniture, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - 1151 Elder Avenue, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - 254 East 174th Street, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - 995-997 East 172nd Street, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - 635 East 211th Street, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Moon Bedding Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - 850-860 Union Avenue et al, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - World Metal Spinning Corporation, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Atlanta Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - New York Jewelry Trade School, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Singer Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Lipsky and Rosenthal, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Roman Silversmiths, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - 35-64 90th Street, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Simplex Cloth Cutting, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Nu-Batts Corporation, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - 436 West 160th Street, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - 387 South 5th Street, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Associated Amusement Machine Operators of New York, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - SS White Dental Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - AAA Television Maintenance, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - Atlantic Baby Carriage, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - Paramount Associated Food Markets, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - North American Aristocrat Baby Carriage Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 46)
  - Scharco Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 47)
  - Kenyon Transformer, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 48)
  - Madisonia Hearth, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 49)
  - Hygrade Products Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 50)
  - Winter and Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 51)
  - Pioneer Woodcraft, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 52)
  - Singer Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 53)
  - 984 Bronx Park Street, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 54)
  - 552 St. Paul's Place, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 55)
  - Dreyer Brothers Home Furnishings, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 56)
  - HA Johnson, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 57)
  - Finn-Cara Plastering Corporation, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 58)
  - Barracini Candy Corporation, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 59)
  - Fanny Farmer Candy Shops, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 60)
  - Singer Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 61)
  - Singer Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 62)
  - Singer Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 63)
  - Madisonia Manikins, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 64)
  - Espey Manufacturing Corporation, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 65)
  - Bee Line, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 66)
  - Monarch Upholstery Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 67)
  - De Nobili Cigar Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 68)
  - Simon Zucker Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 69)
  - 121 Bennett Avenue, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 70)
  - M and W Upholsterers, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 71)
  - C and L Overalls, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 72)
  - Cavalier Upholstery Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 73)
  - Abbott Appliance Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 74)
  - NY Jewelry Trade School, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 75)
  - Eveready Hardware Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 76)
  - 1175 Gerard Avenue, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 77)
  - Interborough News Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 78)
  - Herman's Cake Box, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 79)
  - SS Kresge Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 80)
  - 120 Broadway, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 81)
  - John Reber Baking Corporation, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 82)
  - Three Star Bakery, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 83)
  - Everlast Metal Corporation, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 84)
  - Jacob Tenzer Corporation, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 85)
  - Helton Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 86)
  - 215 east 197th Street, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 87)
  - 44 Fountain Place, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 88)
  - 312 East 168th Street, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 89)
  - 3138 Bailey Avenue, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 90)
  - 1635 Montgomery Avenue, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 91)
  - Steel Scaffolding Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 92)
  - Fruit and Produce Purveyors, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 93)
  - Guardian Electronics Corporation, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 94)
  - Falcon Buick Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 95)
  - 501-505 West 187th Street, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 96)
  - 1874 Loring Place, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 97)
  - Soda Service Corporation, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 98)
- AR 4051 - AR 4350 (1951). (Box 53)
  - 21-31-41 Bennett Avenue, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Ace Leather Goods Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Adams Laboratories et al, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Ladenheim Fixtures, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - London Chemists, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Doric Pharmacy, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - University Chemists, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Elliott Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - 2100 Walton Avenue, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Newmark and Lewis, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Imperial Steel Partition, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - 1556-1558 Hoe Avenue, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Schwartz Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Primrose Bakery, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - United Mattress Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Quality Furniture Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Union News Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Stewart Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Ram Decorators, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Crown Drug Store, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Tru Bilt Cabinet Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Bronx Hardware and Equipment Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Imperial Beverage Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - 3505 Decatur Avenue, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Breakstone Brothers Incorporated, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Bent Steel Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Scott Young Books, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Maison Furniture Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - 375 East 205th Street, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - 2160 Holland Avenue, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - 470-74 Pelham Road, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - 264 Echo Place, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Atlantic Carriage Stores, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - F and S Mounting and Finishing Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Everlast Metal Products Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Utility Products Company and Fin Lee Products Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Chesterfield Music Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - 80 Hanson Place, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - 1295 Grand Concourse, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - US Studio and Mattress Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - 984 East 178th Street, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Pathe Tool Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Economy Drug Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - Unique Chrome Furniture Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Hart Furniture Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Friedland Fixtures, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Interstate Baler Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Stanley Togs, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Walter Motor Truck, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - 2124 Harrison Avenue, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Eagle Plastic Corporation, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - Shaw Television, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - Northside Plating Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 53)
  - Drake Bakeries, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 54)
  - Stanley Kitchen Equipment Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 55)
  - Grennan Bakeries, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 56)
  - Moss Pharmacies, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 57)
  - Olympic Radio and Television, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 58)
  - Rhonnie's Millinery, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 59)
  - Gottfried Baking, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 60)
  - Canada Dry, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 61)
  - Borden's Farm Products, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 62)
  - Automatic Bedding Corporation, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 63)
  - Parke Davis and Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 64)
  - Howard Clothes, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 65)
  - Metal Industries, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 66)
  - Quality Woodworking, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 67)
  - Lorenz and Weide, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 68)
  - Interstate Woodworking Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 69)
  - Glassman Box Corporation, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 70)
  - General Display Case Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 71)
  - Red Circle Display Case Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 72)
  - John A. Johnson Corporation, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 73)
  - Kleon Corporation, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 74)
  - Island Arts, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 75)
  - F and T Trucking Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 76)
  - Joseph Panichella et al, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 77)
  - Pipe Protection Service, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 78)
  - Northside Plating Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 79)
  - Corbetta Construction Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 80)
  - SR Contracting Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 81)
  - Gross Parlor, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 82)
  - Metropolitan Broadcast Company, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 83)
  - La Belle Silver, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 84)
  - Strauss Stores Corporation, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 85)
  - SB Thomas, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 86)
  - Liquidometer Corporation, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 87)
  - 2979 Marion Avenue and 2972 Perry Avenue, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 88)
  - Glasco Luncheonette Food Supply Corporation, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 89)
  - Bent Glass Works, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 90)
  - Kayne Studios, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 91)
  - 44 Court Street, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 92)
  - 1951 (Box 53, Folder 93)
- AR 4351 - AR 4700 (1951). (Box 54)
  - 44 Court Street, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Chelsea Optical Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Eagle Plastic Corporation, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - 769 St. Marks Avenue, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Purified Feather and Down Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Epiphone, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Art Mor Togs, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - J. Markowitz, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Optical Products Corporation, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Roman Silversmiths, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Bronx Boulevard Garage, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - SB Thomas, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Biltmore Foods, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - De Jur Amsco Corporation, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Gordon Baking Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Harjer Furniture, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Wolf Decorators, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - B and F Furniture, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Sunshine Upholstery, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Belmont Parlor Frame, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Monarch Frame, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Altoni Furniture, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Pennington Furniture, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Feature Ring Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - 1444 43rd Street, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - National Cabinet Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Alba De Luxe Upholstery Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Stylecraft Upholstery, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - John Spirito and John Scandiffio, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Colony House, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Somerset Furniture, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Alba De Luxe Upholstery, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Boulevard Upholstery, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Berke Ressler Decorators, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - New York Central Railroad Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Bowman's Bar and Grill, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Affiliated Moving Van Owners, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - Louis Decorators, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - Greenberg Brothers, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - Jewish national Fund, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - National Ornament and Trimming Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - Metal Industries, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - 138 Broadway, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - 1985 East 15th Street, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - Associated Hotel and Residence Clubs, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - George J. Schwartz, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 46)
  - H. Becker Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 47)
  - Simon Rowland Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 48)
  - Able Electric Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 49)
  - Royal Cushions, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 50)
  - I. Axelrod, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 51)
  - G. Milano et al, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 52)
  - Winterland Manufacturing Corporation, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 53)
  - Hygrade Products Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 54)
  - American Cystoscope Makers, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 55)
  - Silverstone Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 56)
  - Old Roumanian Restaurant, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 57)
  - Hilton Optical, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 58)
  - French Powder Puff, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 59)
  - Foremost Dairies, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 60)
  - American Optical Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 61)
  - C. Ludwig Baumann, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 62)
  - M. Ottenheimer's Sons, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 63)
  - General Bronze Corporation, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 64)
  - General Bronze Corporation, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 65)
  - Kroll Brothers, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 66)
  - The Avenue Restaurant, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 70)
  - Warner Furniture, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 71)
  - Floral Decorators, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 72)
  - Harjer Furniture Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 73)
  - BR Upholstery Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 74)
  - 682-4 St. Mary's Street, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 75)
  - Greenlee Motors, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 76)
  - Gude Brothers, Kieffer Company and June Dairy Products Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 77)
  - Coca Cola Bottling Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 78)
  - Ford Instrument, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 79)
  - Garfield News Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 80)
  - General Display Case, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 81)
  - Duffey Buick Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 82)
  - Ford Instrument, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 83)
  - Star Bus Lines, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 84)
  - The Gold Mersereau Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 85)
  - Dictograph Products, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 86)
  - Columbia University, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 87)
  - Robin Sportswear, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 88)
  - S. Schneider and Son, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 89)
  - Standard Keil Hardware Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 90)
  - Purified Feather and Down Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 91)
  - Bay Four Diner, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 92)
  - 10 Hemingway Avenue, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 93)
  - Royal Novelty Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 94)
  - Keystone Silver, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 95)
  - Supreme Steel Products, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 96)
  - Columbia Casualty Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 97)
  - 495 East 174 Street, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 98)
  - 3025 Godwin Terrace, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 99)
  - Great Metal Manufacturing Corporation, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 100)
  - Iron and Steel Products, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 101)
  - Villa Bakery, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 102)
  - 1744-54 Washington Avenue, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 103)
  - 56 Sheridan Avenue, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 104)
  - Woodward Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 105)
  - 106-108 Marcy Place, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 106)
  - 1105-71 Morrison Place, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 107)
  - Schlossman's, Incorporated, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 108)
  - Gazelle Bake Shop, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 109)
  - Carnell Manufacturing, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 110)
  - Astor Chemists, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 111)
  - Atlantic Baby Carriage Stores, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 112)
  - Globe Desk Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 113)
  - Glenmore Novelty Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 114)
  - S. Schneider and Sons, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 115)
  - Gordon Baking Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 116)
  - Ford Instrument Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 117)
  - Kaz Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 118)
  - Superior Optical Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 119)
  - 1951 (Box 54, Folder 120)
- AR 4704 - AR 5200 (1952). (Box 55)
  - Graham Company, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - General Bronze Corporation, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Philip Caesar, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Kay Manufacturing Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Louis Hochberg, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - NY Furniture Merchants Association, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Affiliated Restaurateurs, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Viscuso Bakery and Genga Bakery, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Electronic Transformer, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - American Stamp Manufacturing, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - 2885 Valentine Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - 3215 Bainbridge Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Plaza Pharmacy, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - 1745 Fulton Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - 87 West 169th Street, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - 500 West 190 Street, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - 2160 Bronx Park East, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - M. Mittman, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Savarins, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Tri-boro Combustion, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - 3115 Brighton 4th Street, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Optical Products Corporation, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Chrome Enterprise Corporation, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - 2357 Davidson Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - 1660 Topping Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - 3656 Johnson Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - NY Furniture Merchants, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - East Coast Tileboard, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - London Trunk and Bag, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Dandy Mattress, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - M. Mittman, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Gottfried Baking Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - 1340 Merriam Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - 788 Fox Street, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - 2145 Matthews Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Tick Upholstery Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Sloves Mechanical, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Midway School, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Bronx Box Lunch, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Broadway and 47th Street Corporation, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Herman Upholstery, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - 2703 Webb Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - 2955 Grand Concourse and 203 East 175th Street, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - 1801 Loring Place, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - 2055 Grand Concourse, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Marbro Upholstery Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - Clyde Chemist, Incorporated, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - Eton Chemists, Incorporated, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - Berk-Stevens, Incorporated, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - Block Drug Stores, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - Blog Drug Stores, Incorporated, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - Strand Pharmacy, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - Sheridan Square Chemists, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - 285 South Central Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - Ritz Interior Decorators, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 56)
  - Atlantic Spring Products, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 57)
  - Automatic Bedding Corporation, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 58)
  - Bob's Amusement Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 59)
  - Eveready Hardware Manufacturing, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 60)
  - Murray and Sorensen, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 61)
  - Wells Fargo Armored Services, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 62)
  - Equitable Optical Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 63)
  - Mary Elizabeth Restaurant, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 64)
  - 3824 Bronx Boulevard, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 65)
  - 466 Rockaway Park, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 66)
  - Sleepmaker Products, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 67)
  - Aristocratic Rest Products, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 69)
  - JFD Manufacturing Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 70)
  - East Coast Tileboard, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 71)
  - Borden Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 72)
  - SB Thomas, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 73)
  - Comet Decorators, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 74)
  - Cove Drug et al, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 75)
  - BC Art Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 76)
  - Eagle Plastics Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 77)
  - Eagle Fish Company and Empire State Fish Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 78)
  - J. Carroll, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 79)
  - Ebbers-Hill, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 80)
  - W. Branfman, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 81)
  - 1 Harrison Street, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 82)
  - 1215 Grand Concourse, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 83)
  - Sohmer and Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 84)
  - Murray and Sorensen, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 85)
  - United Retail Fish Dealers, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 86)
  - Stanley Kitchen Equipment, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 87)
  - 2315 Creston Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 88)
  - 463 Pelham Road, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 89)
  - Simon Bernstein's Sons, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 90)
  - Eaves Costume Manufacturing, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 91)
  - Regent Furniture, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 92)
  - Major Cabinet, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 93)
  - Advance Seating Equipment, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 94)
  - Singer Manufacturing Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 95)
  - Singer Manufacturing Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 96)
  - American Zyloptic Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 97)
  - 1440 Undercliff Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 98)
  - Claudette's, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 99)
  - 569 Academy Street, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 100)
  - Borden Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 101)
  - New York Jewelry Trade School, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 102)
  - Standard Keil Hardware, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 103)
  - Roman Silversmiths, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 104)
  - A. Ressa, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 105)
  - Faberge, Incorporated, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 106)
  - Faberge, Incorporated, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 107)
  - Community Opticians, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 108)
  - Somerset Furniture, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 109)
  - Stratford Pen Corporation, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 110)
  - Iron and Steel Products, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 111)
  - Screen-Tek Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 112)
  - 1360-70 Merrian Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 113)
  - Red Coach Grill, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 114)
  - JG Furniture Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 115)
  - 883 Fairmont Place, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 116)
  - Master Barbes et al, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 117)
  - 2270 Walton Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 118)
  - 11117 Manor Avenue, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 119)
  - American Art Furniture, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 120)
  - J. Tannenbaum, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 121)
  - 1295 Grand Concourse, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 122)
  - 4590 Spuyten Duyvil Parkway, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 123)
  - Elite Specialty Metal, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 124)
  - Coca Cola Bottling Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 125)
  - Morey Machinery, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 126)
  - Supreme Steel Products, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 127)
  - Red Circle Display Case Company, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 128)
  - 1952 (Box 55, Folder 129)
- AR 5201 - AR 5599 (1952). (Box 56)
  - M and W Upholsterers, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Rockwell Manufacturing Company, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Berke Bakeries Company, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Starling Upholstery Company, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - 61 West Grand Street, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Will Wood Gardens, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Swiss Radium and Dial Painting, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Gilmore's Steak House, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Star Looseleaf, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Levenson Drug, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - General Baking Company, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Gay Togs, Incorporated, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - 1215 Seneca Avenue, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - 1883 Prospect Avenue, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Singer Manufacturing Company, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Ward Baking Company, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - 1337 Merriam Avenue, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - 1261 Merriam Avenue, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - 1664 Nelson Avenue, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - 2925 Matthews Avenue and 2922 Barnes Avenue, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 20)